Brock's in a pinch.
20:00.
It's time.
It's time. Let's have a cheerful, shiny voice, yes!
Hello, good evening!
Here we go.
Good evening!
We're live!
How many times do you get to do a live broadcast?
The first round of live delivery...
The first drink of the live feed.
Draft beer, right?
I'm not saying it's fresh, I'm just saying...
I mean, the first glass of beer tastes better on draft.
That's what I meant.
Today, too...
This is how it came to be.
I'm having sushi with you.
The other party is
It's a balikada, sir.
No, no, no, no, no...
What is it?
You were sleeping, right?
Just now.
Oh, yeah? We were?
We weren't sleeping? Around.
No, no, no, we weren't sleeping.
Oh, no.
There's a recording.
You were asleep.
You scared me.
I was sleeping in a place that wasn't my house, and when I fell asleep, there was a chord that came on for a second, like a dream, like I was standing alone on Mars or something, and the sun was shining on me.
The sun was shining on me, and I was like...
I was dreaming, right?
You were even dreaming?
I'm a dreamer. I'm a dreamer.
So, I'd like to continue with the recording this week.
Please do.
Yes, so today is Friday, the 23rd of February.
Today is the 23rd of February, which is Friday, and we have a wonderful anniversary.
I love it, and you all love it, too.
Fuji Day!
Mt. Fuji
February 3rd
Fuji, but of course we can see Mt. Fuji in Tokyo, Yokohama, and other places around here, but when I was in Kyushu, I used to see Mt.
When I was in Kyushu, I saw Mt. Fuji on TV or something, but how old were you when you first saw it in person?
But before I entered elementary school, my family took a trip to Yamanashi to see Mt.
From Fukuoka?
Yes.
Thank you for coming all the way.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Did you see it?
I did.
How was it?
It's big.
Yeah, it's big.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's the biggest one.
So, you know...
I'm like...
I don't know how to say it.
I thought you had a tiny one.
But it's true.
I could see quite a bit, too.
Fuji is really big.
I could see it, and I could see it, and I could see it.
Only one shape and everything.
It's truly one-of-a-kind
The one and only.
This is the story of the week, isn't it?
I know, it's just like that, isn't it?
It's like that, isn't it?
So when you grow up and become an adult...
I wonder how people feel when they see Mt. Fuji for the first time.
I guess so.
Fuji on a rope.
I think there is a region in Japan where you can only see Mt. Fuji with a rope.
I think Nagoya and that area is the boundary of the area.
From there, you can see it in logistics.
I thought it must be really impressive when you see it for the first time.
Today is the day of Mt. Fuji.
It's moving a little strange.
I don't know how to say it...
It's not very smooth.
It's like... I see...
Yes. Yes, like that.
And also, you probably think it's cute, right?
I think you probably think it's cute.
Well, you know, this time of year, it's 223 today, the day of Mt.
Fuji is best seen when it's cold or the air is dry.
Yes, it's visible. And it's white, too.
That's right.
It's white, isn't it?
That's what Mt. Fuji is all about, isn't it?
Fuji.
Okay, let's go.
That corner.
What do you think it is?
It's the only one.
Okay, Balicata, please.
Toyoki's Corner.
What's the title?
Imagine a Creature's Corner
I've never seen it start so gradually before.
It's the first time it's ever started this gradually.
It's like, "Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it!
Slowly.
It's like, "You're smoldering.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Today's topic is...
Let's see, it's Kanji again...
Kanji.
I got it from Mr. Monopoly, who is a very good shopper
I was pretending to be...
I'm sorry, Monopoly, I'm a good shopper.
I'm sorry, but I had to let you off the hook this time.
Sorry.
Sorry?
Sorry, we'll just have to celebrate another time. Sorry! We'll celebrate again.
Next time.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let's see...
Yokohama City, Naka Ward
Pokon, good-looking
Thank you very much.
You have an amazing occupation
Passerby in front of TV series
Is your job around here?
That's amazing
It's in Naka-ku.
It's right around the corner.
It's right around there.
Can I go to your home address?
No, no, no.
I didn't know TV didn't allow such things.
If it wasn't live, we could just cut it out.
But we're live now, so it's even worse.
Basically, you're not allowed to say these things.
How long have you been doing this? How long have you been doing this job?
Television is very strict.
It's called compliance.
You know best.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So Mr. Pocon gave me this.
It's in kanji.
May I?
This is it.
Tsubaki elephant.
This is the kanji for a certain creature...
But it's an elephant, but it's not an elephant, is it?
An elephant that might be an elephant.
It's not an elephant.
Master Bau
I've never been called "Bau" before.
I say it all the time.
I'm quite happy to be called Bau.
Bau is for that kind of thing.
Camellia elephants, right?
Camellia elephant.
I don't know if you know...
Camellia elephant, that's what it is, if you know what I'm talking about... camellia elephant.
Wow!
I really don't get it.
YouTube is awesome... and other stuff.
I wonder...
I don't know, but you know a lot about it, don't you?
Really?
I guess it's something unexpected, isn't it?
It's something unexpected, isn't it?
It's unexpected, isn't it?
By the way...
I'm sure you've both seen it before.
I think we've both seen it before.
What?
Maybe you've even touched it.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
I mean, maybe.
Maybe.
By the way, I've seen it and I've touched it.
Have you?
Yes, I have.
Heh.
By the way, camellias are in spring? Camellia is spring?
Camellia?
I don't know.
You're right, you're right.
Did you get it? Shall we go? Shall we go?
Well, you got it, too, sir? It's done.
That's great.
Would you like to go?
Shall we go?
You're working fast these days, doctor.
Yes, I have to write a little earlier after all.
I'll take care of it.
Here's the Tsubaki statue.
This way, Pan.
What's this? A hidden creature?
A snake?
Yes, sir.
But it looks like a camellia with gills.
Right here.
Wow, it's kinda cool.
I don't know. I think it's a kind of snake.
It's okay that it looks like this now, but when it's like this, it's a bit of a nuisance, isn't it?
Yes, it looks like elephant ears.
Or camellia...
When it's like this, it looks like a camellia.
It also looks like a camellia.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought there might be a snake like this.
I see, so it's a snake.
Snake, a snake.
Then the balicata...
I didn't know what it was anymore.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I'm a little scared of a lot of things.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I made a mistake. I drew a flower when there was a flower.
That's the correct answer.
This is not a parent-child relationship.
Not father and son.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Yes, yes.
Well, this is... well, well, well...
Can I just give you an idea of what we see?
Yes.
This could be a camellia, maybe, just maybe.
Maybe. This represents an elephant.
A camellia elephant.
That's very insightful.
Well, well, well, well.
These are ears.
The feet.
And these...
This one...
And they're both drawn with conviction, and there's a foot, and what's this?
And they're both drawn with conviction.
That's right.
You know when an elephant's tail goes "boho"?
Elephant boho!
That tail...
What?
Raise it.
Is there such a memorable scene?
When the elephant's tail is raised... is there such a memorable scene?
The elephant?
Not so bad.
I'm sure there is.
I see.
Is this a poacher's house? He was shot in a poacher's house.
You're bleeding.
Some elephants have their eyes on the poachers.
It's dangerous!
I'll tell you what...
The answer is... secret fishermen are dangerous!
It's a seagull.
It looks like a statue of a stinkbug.
I think it's probably the tip of a stink bug, because it looks like a flower on the statue.
Maybe that's what it is.
I'm just guessing.
It's too realistic and a little creepy.
It's too realistic.
I'm running a bug chart right now.
I'd rather have it changed to balicata, balicata style.
The usual balicata flavor.
Please do!
Oh, wait a minute.
It's good.
What does it look like?
Vertical writing.
You've seen stinkbugs, right?
Yes, I have.
I've touched one.
Unwillingly
You say it smells really bad, right?
It's really...
Like, "What's this?
That's right.
He's amazing!
I think it's something you do when the enemy is coming.
But it's cool to release a stinky smell or poison just because an enemy is coming.
It's cool that he can emit a stinky smell or poison.
Special Ability
How about this?
Peace, peace, peace... it's not even in its original form.
Pineapple... and what is the texture of this?
What's this?
Oh, a persimmon...
Well, well, well... That's what I'm talking about.
That's right.
That's great.
Turtles.
I like it. It looks like a pirupple.
I can't believe it's the same thing again like this
Yes, yes, yes, yes, thank you.
Have you ever touched or seen a Varicata stinkbug?
I have.
I don't think so.
People say you're not supposed to touch them.
That's right.
They smell so bad.
The smell is indescribable.
It's a bit traumatic.
It smells fishy... and it's like, let's say, "pak choi".
It's the same as "pak choi".
It's like a lot of green stuff that smells fishy.
I'm sure you've been attacked by stinkbugs before.
There are some idiots who go out of their way to touch them... like me.
I wondered what they smelled like.
But there are times when you unintentionally touch it, just to see what it smells like.
Yes, that's true.
There are times when they often stick to laundry, aren't they?
That's right, when there's a big outbreak.
When the eye worms come again, in droves, in such large numbers.
So now let's take over the job.
If you have any ideas, please keep sending them to us.
If you have any suggestions, please keep sending them to us.
I also have an announcement for those of you who are watching the live broadcast.
Right now...............................
Tickets are on sale now!
VIP reservations are on sale now!
What do you mean "reservation flow"?
Like, "I made a reservation, but..."? Is there?
There are still some VIP tickets left.
Here's your chance! I'd love to see you all in the VIPs.
I'd love to meet you all in the VIP.
You know what I said before.
What I really want you to do is...
There are a lot of regulars here at the Devil's Den.
Of course, their pseudonyms match their real faces.
Of course, there are many people whose pseudonyms match their real faces.
But there are also people who don't recognize you.
Like, "Oh, you're that guy.
That's why I'd like you to put something here.
I'd like you to put a nameplate here.
I'd like you to put a nametag on it, or something like that, so people know who I am.
I'd like you to tell me.
I'd love to hear your theory.
Thank you very much.
So, the VIP oil is a perk for coming to the show.
A perk for coming to the show.
And that sakosh!
There it is!
Sakosh!
This is it, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Sacoche.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Isn't it wonderful?
Yes, it is.
There's something in here.
It's great.
You can put things in it.
Yes, that's right.
It's transparent, so you can see what's in it.
That's right.
Even if a stink bug were to wander in here...
They'll know it's a stink bug.
So it's safe.
And it's safe.
On the back, it's just like the poster.
What's changed?
They were side by side, weren't they?
The special offer for visitors is this.
The perks are different from what they're selling.
I don't get it.
That's right.
Vip said he'd put a seagull in the gift bag.
I went to pick it up that day.
It's an incident.
That's how it happened.
Please come!
So, this is the gift for the show.
Is this the very same perk of coming to the show?
A bonus sakosh.
I was waiting for you in the Rip S seat.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes.
So, we continue with Metacana Devil.
Well, it's almost time, though, isn't it?
Yes, it's about a month from now.
Yes, and you have a variety of goods, including the Sakosh.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a lot of things that you'd like to show us.
I'd like to show you some of the actual goods.
This is it, isn't it?
Should I show you something?
Who's this handsome guy?
Who is it?
This is my actor.
Oh!
Master, he's really cool.
He's so cool, guys.
Hold up your guitars!
He looks so cool!
And...
Ready, set, go!
Nice to meet you on the main island.
Hi! Good morning! Please! Good morning!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's good.
Pose in a very intense way.
Intense!
That's great.
Like this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's good.
This time, all of you.
You all have great poses, each of you.
I'm going to see Balikata!
Mr. Birchy...
And Mr. Gashikashi...
Mr. Gashikashi has asked for a replacement balikata.
It's a little bit late for the day.
Yes, I'm thinking of doing it, so please look forward to it.
I'm sure we'll have fun on the day of the event.
I'm sure you'll be able to enjoy the show with us.
The pose is a bit too individualistic, isn't it?
Very good.
It's great to see them all lined up like this.
I'm so thankful... I'm so thankful to be able to see them...
If it were me, everyone would just click on it.
It's the way it should be!
I'd love to have a badge like this...
That's right...
I don't know...
Yes, yes, yes...
This is mine.
Wow!
Here it is.
Yuuhi Zadar!
I'm looking forward to a great Devil's Charge!
Thank you for the deville charge!
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
By all means, by all means, by all means...
Yes, by all means.
You mean you can put this badge in the transparent part of the sakosh, right?
That's right.
What do you call it?
That's not a seagrass pit.
Is it really so limited?
I thought it'd be funny to use it like a bug cage.
What's it called?
It's written "itabac"... itabac... itabac...
I have no idea what it means... but there used to be "ita-vehicle"...
It's a word that used to mean "ita-guruma," or "itaba. It's a back version of that, like itababa.
Itaba. I see. I see. I see. By all means. So you've already put all of your own wonderful things into it.
Can I buy it now? Perhaps.
Yes, yes. I'm just saying that the sample is ready.
Oh, I see. You can't buy it anymore? It's already closed.
Oh, no.
But you see, people are already buying.
That's right.
Let's make it snappy.
That means you clicked on it, right?
Thank you very much.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This badge, on the other hand, is a little bit more...
There's a lot of cute poses on this badge.
Yes, it's cute.
Cute.
It's nice.
That's the one... the one with the date change.
It's beautiful.
The date game.
The dividing line.
If you go this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way.
This way, this way.
Awesome yes
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I hope you're all looking forward to getting it.
Oh, yes.
It's a good thing, isn't it?
Well, well, well.
So, is this how it's going to be in Nanfi shi?
That's right.
Let's wrap it up.
I knew you'd say that.
Yes, that's right.
I'm off next week.
I'll be back next week.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but there's something that's happened to Young.
Young's very popular situation
I have to take a break.
Can I tell you why?
It's a Young Adult situation.
It's an adult situation.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Yes, it is.
It's just...
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, then...
Next week...
Next week?
I'm in a bit of agony.
Yeah.
Why don't you just watch TVK's "Palipi Komei" or something?
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
That's what I said.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
The last one, then.
I'd like to ask the audience to prepare.
Yes, that's right.
From now on...
Okay.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
Okay, last one, please.
Yes, please.
Balicata.
Bon appétit.
See you next week.
There is no next week.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.